Charlotte Wesley Holloman Papers 140
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
- Series 1
  - Historia di Jephte, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - John Lennon and Paul McCartney, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Bethoven, Undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - My Favorite Spirituals, Undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Art Songs, Spaeth, Undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Judas Maccabaeus, Undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Magnificant, Undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Faure Requiem, Undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - J.S Bach, Undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - The Messiah, Undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Elijah, an Oratorio, Undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - The Creation, Hayden, Undated (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Course and Organization, Undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Misc Compositions, Undated (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - La Flora, Volume Secondo, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Fifty Modern English Songs, Undated (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - One Hundred Songs of England, Undated (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Roland Hayes, 1954-2011 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Purcell, Undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Fifty Mastersongs, Undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Music (1 of 4), Undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Music (2 of 4), Undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Music (3 of 4), Undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Music (4 of 4), Undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Recordings/Albums, Undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Recordings/Albums, Undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Recordings/Albums, Undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Recordings/Albums, Undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Recordings/Albums, Undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Recordings/Albums, Undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Framed photographs, Undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Voice teacher award, Undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Recordings/Albums, Undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Recordings/Albums, Undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Video and audio recordings, Undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Music CDs, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Music CDs, Undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Books and appointment book, Undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Books miscellaneous, Undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Mozart Sheet Music, Undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - La Boheme Sheet Music, 1830 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Donizetti's Lucrezia Borgia Sheet Music, Undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Folk Songs and Stories of the Americas, Undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Latin American Festivals and Folk Dance, Undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Opera-In-Concert, Undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - English Fundamentals Sheet Music, 1933 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Practical Beginning Theory, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Puccini La Boheme Sheet Music, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - The Stories of Rigoleete and Manon, Undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - B. Schott's Sohne Sheet Music, 1894 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Martha of the Fair at Richmond, Undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Fra Diavolo, Undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Cuban Cutie Sheet Music, 1950 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - The Merry Widow Sheet Music, Undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Compositions For the Piano Sheet Music, 1944 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Compositions For the Piano Sheet Music, 1946 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Compositions For the Piano Sheet Music, 1946 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Compositions For the Piano Sheet Music, 1950 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Memoire Sheet Music, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - The Singing Fountain Sheet Music, Undated (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Mammoth Collection of Famous Children's Songs, 1939 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - The Crimson Sap Song Cycle Sheet Music, Undated (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Four Movements Sheet Music, 1948 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - A Slight Case of Ivory Sheet Music, 1943 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Mechanical Designs Sheet Music, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Rachmaninoff Sheet Music, 1955 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Bazzars of Bagdad Sheet Music, Undated (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Chopin Polonaise Sheet Music, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Americana Sheet Music, 1929 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Soliloquy Sheet Music, 1927 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Tchaikowsky Sheet Music, 1955 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Raphling Piano Sonata Sheet Music, 1958 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Catalogue of Music For Chorus Sheet Music, Undated (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Rachmaninoff Sheet Music 1955 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Faculty Handbook and Library Guide, Undated (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - A Singing of Angels, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Chorus Vocal Scores Libretti, Undated (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Music for Voice, Undated (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Choral Guide, Undated (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - The Maiden and the Passer-by Sheet Music, Undated (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - My Evening Prayer Sheet Music, Undated (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - "Never" Sheet Music, 1951 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - A Holiday in Paris Sheet Music, Undated (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - There is No Christmas Like a Home Christmas Sheet Music, 1950 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - With All My Heart and Soul Sheet Music, 1951 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - Candidez Sheet Music, 1947 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - Apretaitos Sheet Music, 1947 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Pedazo de Noche Sheet Music, 1947 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - Bendicion y Castigo Sheet Music, 1947 (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - Pensamento Sheet Music, 1947 (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - Rafael Mendez Sheet Music, 1949 (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - The Emperor's New Clothes Sheet Music, Undated (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - Richard Magner Sheet Music, Undated (Box 49, Folder 41)
  - Untitled Sheet Music, Undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - L'Anello Del Nibelungo, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Der Rosenkavalier Sheet Music, Undated (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Jacques Offenbach Sheet Music, 1949 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Tristan and Isolada Sheet Music, Undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Songs That Never Grow Old Sheet Music, Undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Richard Wagner Sheet Music, 1906 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Christmas Cheer Sheet Music, 1957 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - "Louise" Sheet Music, Undated (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Madame Butterfly Sheet Music, 1904 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Favorite Christmas Carols Sheet Music, Undated (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Untitled Program Cut Out, Undated (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Blue Monday (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Christmas Party Sheet Music, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Chestnuts Roasting on An Open Fire Sheet Music, Undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Santa Clus is Comin To Town Sheet Music, 1934 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - The Twelve Days of Christmas Sheet Music, Undated (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - White Christmas Sheet Music, 1942 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Richard Wagner Sheet Music, Undated (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Cavalleria Rusticana Sheet Music, Undated (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - New Approaches to Music in the Elementary School, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Video and audio recordings, Undated (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Video and audio recordings, Undated (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Metronome, Undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Clock, Undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Ceramic Bird, Undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Wooden Photo of Holloman, Undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Seiko Quartz Metronome, Undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Pitch Pipe, Undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Video and audio recordings, Undated (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Video and audio recordings, Undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Video and audio recordings, Undated (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Sheet music, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Sheet music, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Ben Holt Memorial Scholarship, 2011 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - DC Council Letter, 2012 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - National Association of Negro Musicans, 2015 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Howard University Retiree Appreciation Program, 2013 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Howard Retirement Letter, 2013 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - White House Letter, Undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Partners Achieving Success, 2014 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - "Doctors Without Borders", 2015 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Holloman Photos, 2013 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Vocal Arts Competition for Emerging Artists, 2014 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Letter from Holloman, Undated (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - National Visionary Leadership Project, Undated (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Sigma Alpha Iota Program, 2015 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Day declaration, Undated (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Certificates and awards, Undated (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Posters, Undated (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Certificates and awards, Undated (Box 61)
  - Scrapbook, Undated (Box 61)
  - Plaques, Undated (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Grove's Dictionary of Music and Musicians, 5th ed., 8 volume set, Undated (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Awards, Undated (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Awards, Undated (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Books miscellaneous, Undated (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Small books, Undated (Box 68, Folder 1)